breaking news a murder has been
discovered at Salinas Valley on August
16 1930 at 4:20 p.m. during the time the
body was discovered a group of men were
trying to pursue a murder murder of
Curly's Tyler's wife they which they
suspected to be mr. Lenny smalls the
reason for the suspicion is that
Curley's wife had a broken neck and mr.
Ling small being known for his brute
strength
points all the evidence toward mr.
Small's the body was identified as mr.
Lenny smalls he he was over six feet he
was well over six feet tall and had a
gunshot wound on the back of his head
the bullet shell found here at the body
was identified to be used by the gun
stolen for Miss mr. Carson Smith mr.
Kirk mr. curly tyler and mr. Carson
Smith had to form the sheriff that
George Milton book was the one who shot
mr. Small's after miss after mr. slim
Johnson and mr. George Milton went to a
local bar to have a drink the police had
enough evidence to perform an arrest on
on George Milton and he is on trial now
for first-degree murder and back to you
Jon George Melton's a migrant worker as
may accuse the first-degree murder of
his friend Lenny small who was a maggot
work information continues to unfold
showing evidence that raises suspicions
that George is responsible for Lenny
smalls death George Miller and Lenny
smalls were close friends that were
traveling the country looking for a job
before they found a job on the honor
ranch in Salinas Valley Valley where
they worked for $50 a month
Lenny smalls has a intellectual
disability
and was taken care of by his aunt in
Auburn California until she died after
his aunt died George Nolan took full
responsibility of money when he was big
and muscular and often had trouble
controlling his strength the accident
only broke and broke his co-workers
hands and his wife's neck and killed
lots of animals Georgia Mellon was
accused of murdering Lennie small the
trial will take place on March 1st and
the following people are the prosecution
witnesses John Carlson marine Chuck
Curley and the following people the
following people are on the defense team
or the defense witness is Josiah candy
slim Frank and George