 Today o n the second day of the trial, Josiah Lincoln took the stand to b e questioned. This 
took place a t about 9 :0 0 A M. Josiah Lincoln is a long time worker o n the farm, but didn't really 
talk to anyone accept Slim Johnson, who’s another witness o n the trail. But, for the short period 
of time that Mr. Milton and Mr. Small were o n the ranch, Josiah saw them to b e very close like 
brothers, this was very unusual a t the time for two people to travel together. George took care of 
Lennie, and Josiah didn't think that he used him to get jobs. On the day o f the incident Mr. Small 
wandered into Jo sia h's barn and talked to him about the “ dream” that Mr. Milton and him had 
shared. The “ dream” is something that they had been planning for a while, they were going to 
buy some land and live o n it in total freedom. After the incident had happened with Jane Tyler 
and Lennie Small, the guys o n the Tyler Ranch wanted to kill Lennie. Mr. Milton didn't know 
what to do , so he killed Lennie because he cared for him and wanted Len n ie’s death to b e b y 
someone he was close to . He wanted him to have a quick and painless death in the hands of 
someone who cared for him, rather than all the guys looking to kill him. Josiah did not believe 
that Mr. Milton committed the murder.

              B y, Cara Ia n n uzzi and Keelin Lally

